https://www.creativedisplays.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyPage top image size: 1000 x 500 px At Creative Displays, Inc., the privacy and protection of your personal and financial information is very important to us. That’s why we’ve created this privacy statement which fully describes our information gathering and dissemination practices. It’s the best way we can demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.Creative Displays, Inc. uses your personal information for the following purposes:Building your CreativeDisplays.com accountFacilitating the ordering processPersonalizing delivery of the content contained within our SiteThose who communicate with Creative Displays, Inc and supply us with contact information may receive future communications by email, direct mail, or telephone. If you do not wish to receive correspondence from Creative Displays, Inc, you can contact us with a request to be removed from our mailing list.Use of Your InformationWhen you register with our site, we ask for your name and e-mail address. Then we ask you to create a password to allow you secure access. We use this to:Process and track your ordersSend order and shipping confirmation emailsIf you choose to receive emails about special offers, we will also:Send catalogs you have requested and mailings that may be of interest to you, provided you have not requested otherwiseSend exclusive email offers of new product announcements and special promotions, provided you have not opted out of receiving these notificationsWe may also use information from your account based on your site visits to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use, which may be shown to affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, successors, and partners. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information and your identity will be kept anonymous. Certain confidential information–such as passwords and credit card numbers– is not disclosed in any of these reports.If you purchase a product or service from Creative Displays, Inc., the information you give–such as your credit card number, purchase information, and contact information–is provided to the banking merchant. Details regarding the purchase are supplied to the distributor or vendor partner. This is necessary to complete the transaction.We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, under circumstances required by law, or–in limited cases–to our business partners as outlined in this policy.You will not be contacted directly by any third party as a result of your relationship with Creative Displays, Inc. unless you have given us permission to do so. Any business partners with whom we share your information will be subject to confidentiality restrictions preventing them from sharing your personal information with others.Security PrecautionsOur site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.When you transmit credit card information to complete a purchase or verify data, we always transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use the industry standard 128-bit SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.In addition to our encryption standards, your CreativeDisplays.com account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. Please do not disclose your password to anyone. Always remember to sign out of your CreativeDisplays.com account and close your browser window when your transactions are complete. This helps keep your account safe.While we strive to protect your personal information, no data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, CreativeDisplays.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information during transmission to or from our site, and you submit information to us at your own risk. Further, CreativeDisplays.com cannot warrant the security for information on our servers or other the other computer systems that we utilize. However, we do our best to ensure the highest level of security on our systems.CookiesWe are committed to providing personalized products and services to you. In order to do so, CreativeDisplays.com uses cookies to store a unique identifier. A cookie is defined as a small amount of text that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. If your browser is configured to enable cookies, then your browser adds the text sent to the appropriate file.CreativeDisplays.com uses cookies to tell us that you have visited our site before, to automatically display information you have requested, and to keep track of the items in your cart (shopping cart). They are used to help us simplify and enhance your shopping experience. A cookie may also be used to tailor ad content both on the site you are visiting as well as other sites within that network that you may visit in the future.Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the Internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our Site. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html or third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).DisclaimerAll interactions with Creative Displays, Inc., are governed by the Terms and Conditions, which can be found on our Site. By interacting with or doing business with Creative Displays, you agree to the Terms and Conditions. The Terms and Conditions are subject to change without notice.Ultimately, you are held responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Always be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.This site contains links to other sites. Creative Displays, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites.Privacy Policy ChangesIf we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Site.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Further, by using this Site, you agree to the Terms and Conditions which can be found on our Site.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Creative Displays, Inc. 16210 Foster St. Overland Park, KS 66085 1-800-733-9617Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping. If you have any issues, you can also contact us at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@creativedisplays.com.At Creative Displays, Inc., the privacy and protection of your personal and financial information is very important to us. That’s why we’ve created this privacy statement which fully describes our information gathering and dissemination practices. It’s the best way we can demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.Creative Displays, Inc. uses your personal information for the following purposes:Building your CreativeDisplays.com accountFacilitating the ordering processPersonalizing delivery of the content contained within our SiteThose who communicate with Creative Displays, Inc and supply us with contact information may receive future communications by email, direct mail, or telephone. If you do not wish to receive correspondence from Creative Displays, Inc, you can contact us with a request to be removed from our mailing list.
Back to Home InfoAbout UsMarkets We ServeBlogHoliday Lighting CatalogHoliday Display CatalogCustomer supportContact UsLogin / RegisterRequest a QuoteTerms and ConditionsOrdering, Shipping, and ReturnsPrivacy PolicyFINANCING AVAILABLESubscribeEmail (required) *Select list(s) to subscribe toGENERAL INTEREST (MASTER) I would like to receive emails from Creative DisplaysConstant Contact Use.By submitting this form, you are consenting to receive marketing emails from: Creative Displays, Inc., 16210 Foster, Stilwell, KS, 66085, http://www.creativedisplays.com. You can revoke your consent to receive emails at any time by using the SafeUnsubscribe® link, found at the bottom of every email. Emails are serviced by Constant ContactPayment Options Copyright 2020 | Creative Displays | All Rights Reserved
X
